[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "AW Root Beer  inspired a restaurant chain.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Valletta is the capital city of this island country in the Mediterranean.", "correct_answer": "Malta", "incorrect_answers": ["Majorca", "Corsica", "Cyprus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how many people attended the soccer match between Uruguay and Brazil during the 1950 FIFA World Cup tournament?", "correct_answer": "199,800", "incorrect_answers": ["300,000", "500,000", "1,000,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On what major holiday is the sweet bread Tsoureki eaten in Greece?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Easter", "New Years Eve", "Christmas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Water is a powerful conductor of electricity.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meal is the bammy, which originates from Jamaica?", "correct_answer": "Bread", "incorrect_answers": ["Dessert", "Boiled meat", "Soup"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Johnny say to Dr Houseman near the end of the film Dirty Dancing?", "correct_answer": "Nobody puts Baby in a corner.", "incorrect_answers": ["Nobody does it better than you.", "Nobody makes me feel like a woman.", "Nobody puts that chair there."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This US city, whose original name was Terminus, is the county seat of Fulton County.", "correct_answer": "Atlanta", "incorrect_answers": ["Omaha", "Savannah", "Orono"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the only outlaw in the film 3:10 to Yuma who doesnt participate in the initial raid on the stagecoach?", "correct_answer": "Ben Wade", "incorrect_answers": ["Charlie Prince", "Tommy Darden", "Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the Baseball Hall of Fame located?", "correct_answer": "Cooperstown, N.Y", "incorrect_answers": ["New York, NY", "Hoboken, NJ", "Canton, OH"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People use a kind of microbe to make this.", "correct_answer": "Bread", "incorrect_answers": ["Mineral water", "Orange juice", "Plastics"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These raptors are known for their unusually social behavior. They even hunt in groups while the majority of raptors are solitary hunters.", "correct_answer": "Harris Hawk", "incorrect_answers": ["Golden Eagle", "Turkey Vulture", "Spotted Owl"]}]